It's Amanda Seals here, joined by...
I am Nails. Happy Friday.
Now, you said you were going to tell us this little story
because we have our Gen Z historian that stopped through earlier this month for Black History Month.
It is a big moment that we need to celebrate real quick.
Well, we have been celebrating our Black History Month with a segment called Bet You Didn't Know,
and we invited Gen Z historian Khalil Green to join us to share some little known Black facts.
And it is great to see that he has taken his influencer content that is really rooted in sharing knowledge and information to the next level,
and he is joining the new Nickelodeon reboot of Nick News as a correspondent.
Oh, my gosh. Yo! Yo!
Yeah. Now, you know, I am a Nickelodeon alum. I'm a Nickelodeon alum, and so welcome to the fam.
But I just love this, Nails, because we talk so much about how important it is to have, like, information that is accurate, et cetera.
But the kids need accurate information, too!
Yeah, and you mentioned how Gen Z is this generation that is just very...
They're active. They're the ones on the front line, and they're just jumping up there.
But this is so dope that Nickelodeon is bringing this back.
And I don't think we had anything like this in quite some time,
but we know that the kids love learning on the TikToks and the Instagrams.
We see it. We see it.
So I think this is beautiful, and I love to see that Khalil is involved.
He's a very smart, thoughtful young Black man.
So I really feel like Nickelodeon did a great job by just even involving him.